(function(){
  var data = touchtile.data;
  data.sakyu = [
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 I-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 I-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-2'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 I-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 I-2'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-2'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 G-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 G-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 T-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 T-2'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 I-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 I-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 H-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 H-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 T-1', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 T-1'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 H-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 H-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 G-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 G-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 O-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 O-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 N-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 N-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 O-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 O-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 N-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 N-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 H-8', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 H-8'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 T-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 T-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 T-8', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 T-8'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 T-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 T-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 H-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 H-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 T-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 T-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 F-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 F-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 M-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 M-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 N-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 N-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 N-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 N-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 M-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 M-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 M-11', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 M-11'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 T-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 T-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-9', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-9'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-9', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-9'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-10', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-10'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-11', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-11'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-10', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-10'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-10', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-10'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 M-10', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 M-10'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-9', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-9'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 M-9', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 M-9'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-8', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-8'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-8', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-8'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-8', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-8'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 M-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 M-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 M-12', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 M-12'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-12', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-12'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 G-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 G-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 H-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 H-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 F-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 F-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 G-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 G-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 H-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 H-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 M-8', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 M-8'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 N-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 N-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 O-8', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 O-8'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 M-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 M-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 M-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 M-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 P-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 P-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 P-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 P-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 O-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 O-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 O-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 O-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 D-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 D-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 D-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 D-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 C-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 C-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-16', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-16'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-15', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-15'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 L-14', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 L-14'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 G-10', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 G-10'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 G-8', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 G-8'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 G-9', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 G-9'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 F-9', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 F-9'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 E-6', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 E-6'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 H-9', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 H-9'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-12', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-12'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-11', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-11'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-12', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-12'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-11', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-11'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 T-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 T-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 H-10', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 H-10'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-15', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-15'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 J-14', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 J-14'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 K-14', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 K-14'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 F-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 F-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 E-7', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 E-7'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 F-8', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 F-8'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 I-1', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 I-1'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 G-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 G-2'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 H-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 H-2'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 B-1', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 B-1'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 C-1', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 C-1'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 B-0', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 B-0'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 A-1', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 A-1'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 E-5', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 E-5'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 A-0', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 A-0'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 B-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 B-2'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 D-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 D-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 E-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 E-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 G-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 G-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 F-4', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 F-4'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 F-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 F-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 D-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 D-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 E-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 E-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 C-3', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 C-3'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 C-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 C-2'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 D-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 D-2'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 F-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 F-2'},
    {'question': '鳥取砂丘 E-2', 'answer': '鳥取砂丘 E-2'}
  ];
})();
